<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Birthday💕</string>
    <string name="flash">"HAPPY\nBIRTHDAY"</string>
    <string name="selfie">"Finally, I found the prettiest person in the whole goddamn world\n\nHere is a picture of the person and yes this is the best I have ever known"</string>
    <string name="reading">"Below are some random quotes and lines that I wanted to share with you\n"</string>
    <string name="bitwawish">"Messages from your loved ones"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche">"“Count your life by smiles, not tears. Count your age by friends, not years. Happy birthday!” - Mother"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche2">"“Happy birthday! I hope all your birthday wishes and dreams come true.” - Father"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche3">"“A wish for you on your birthday, whatever you ask may you receive, whatever you seek may you find, whatever you wish may it be fulfilled on your birthday and always. Happy birthday!”
 - Sister"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche4">"“ Another adventure filled year awaits you. Welcome it by celebrating your birthday with pomp and splendor. Wishing you a very happy and fun-filled birthday!” - Brother"</string>
    <string name="minionWishTrans">"Let’s be honest, one day isn’t enough of a celebration for someone like you. Enjoy your birthday month! - Mimi \n\nHappy birthday to the only person I can hang out with for hours without getting annoyed. - Anonymous \n\nHonestly, I feel bad for everyone else who doesn’t get to have you as a best friend. What a lame life! - Anonymous \n\nMay this year be as satisfying as the cool side of the pillow. - Eren \n\nBecause it’s your birthday, I’ll let you control the music in my car. Use this privilege wisely! - Kenny \n\nHappy birthday to a charming, smart and all-around amazing person. Takes one to know one! - Jess \n\nHappy birthday to the only person who will be truly honest with me when my outfit is not working. - Penny \n\nWe’ve made so many wonderful memories togethers. Cheers to many more. Happy birthday! - Giselle \n\nHappy birthday to one of the most special people in my life. Wishing you many more. - Edwine \n\nToday should be a national holiday because it’s the day my best friend was born! - Jeff \n\nDo you hear that? That’s me screaming happy birthday to my best friend! - Anonymous "</string>
    <string name="minionWish">"You are the strongest support in my life, and I am blessed to have a true friend like you who has always stood by me through the most challenging times. Sometimes I feel that had you not been there in my life, it would have been such a boring and dull life. You are the cheese to my pizza and maple syrup to my pancake because I cannot imagine my life without you. I still look back to when I first met you in kindergarten, and we connected instantly. Nobody would have thought that we will come this far, but now I know that we are friends for life and no matter what happens in the future, we are always going to stick around. It is not easy to live with you, but it is all the more difficult to live without you. You are that friend to me who will first laugh at me when I fall and then come to help me. But no matter how crazy and weird you are, you will always be my special friend and will find me right next to you. On your birthday, I wish that all your dreams come true and you are showered with happiness and success in life."</string>
    <string name="dogWishReal">"Dog noise"</string>
    <string name="reading">Cheer you up with the jokes below! 😝  \n </string>
    <string name="bitwawish">"Hello,Enter your message here"</string>
    <string name="bitwawishneeche">"Enter small special message here"</string>
    <string name="minionWishTrans">"Hello Dear,\n\nI am Kevin. Stuart and Bob are also with me.\n\nWe saw a news headline in the Minions' Daily about the birthday of the cutest person in the world. We know it is you.\n\nWe love you.....We love you more than bananas.\n\nWe would love to come to you for your birthday and yes we want a huge banana party with a banana cake and a banana clown and YOU.\n\nWe were finding ways to contact you then we came across this dude Animesh and he agreed to give our message to you.I wish he doesn't mess things up this time.\n\nWe love you Dear.May God bless you with lots and lots of love and BANANAS.\n\n\n'Hey BOB...BOB don't eat that.Thats not chocolate.Thats poop.Idiot.'\n\n'I'm sorry. Bob keeps doing these things'\n\n'Let me...Let me'\n\n'Okay.Take this'\n\n'Helloooooooo uuummmmmmmmhhhhhhh'\n\n'Happy Birthday...Happy Birthday...Happy Birthday'\n\n'We love you...We love you more than BANANAS'\n\nByeeee...Cyaaa...uuummmmaaaahhh"</string>
    <string name="minionWish">"Bello Dear,\n\ni am lum.  Fouwet yee yok nama bigo com me. \n\nwe ma a daga ripupo een ta minions' rad cama ta oflit de ta cutest pappala een ta globo.  Pem cono pik tis to. \n\nwe ern to. Pem ern to mas pan bananas. \n\nwe polo ern da po da to nunu tu oflit yee si pem quer a hog banana ion com a banana bak yee a banana clown yee to. \n\nwe fem budgan nut da koabo to pen pem lemar bodbag ba dude animesh yee le fibnah da pona noor dogjay da to. Ka jay le hapire mo errec aka ba veela. \n\nwe ern to you. Maybo nos bless to com ism yee ism de ern yee bananas. \n\n\n'hey yok. Yok domo ads pak. Thats non chocolate. Thats poop. Idiot. '\n\n'i'm bido.  Yok par mido les errec'\n\n'let me. Seep me'\n\n'okay. Nupi ba'\n\n'helloooooooo uuummmmmmmmhhhhhhh'\n\n'happy oflit. Fid oflit. Fid oflit'\n\n'we ern to. Pem ern to mas pan bananas'\n\nbyeeee. Cyaaa. uuummmmaaaahhh"</string>
    <string name="dogWishReal">"Bho bhau,\n\naaaaiii aarrrggghhhh bhao bho bhau bhao aargh\n\nargh aaaaaiiiii\n\naaargh bho bho bho bho\n\naaaaiii aarrrggghhhh bhao bho bhau bhao aargh argh aaaaaiiiii\n\naaargh bho bho bho bho\n\naarrrggghhhh bha bho pewpewpew bhow bhow\n\naarrrggghh\n\nbho bho bho hhaarrrggghhhh\n\nbhau bhau bahu bhau babhau bhau aargh argh argh\n\nargh agh aai bhau bhau bhao bho bho bho\n\nBHO BHO"</string>
    <string name="dogWishTrans">"Hello Dear,\n\nMy name is Dogo.\nBut you can call me anything you want.\n\nWell...\n\nYou might know me as I am from your neighbourhood. Me and my friends watch you everyday and make sure no one hurts you.\n\nYes, I am the same light brown coloured dog that sometimes follow you.\n\nYou know when I came to know that your birthday is coming soon, I wanted to wish you,But feared that you might run away thinking I am gonna bite you.\n\nThis wish is made possible because of a very strange phenomena.\n\nThere was this unusual boy who was wandering around your house on a cold evening. I hated him, so me and my friends decided to chase him down so that he never comes back ever. As we were running and following his scooty, all my friends slowly changed their minds and I was left alone in this manhunt. But I quitely followed him to his house and then when the moment came I barked my lungs out.\n\nHe was afraid but strangely and unbelievably we reached to a deal. He promised to make a translator for me. Yes. From bho bho to english.\n\nHe turned out to be a really nice guy. This is all because of him that I am sending my wishes and messages to my best and lovely friend.\n\nDon't ever worry, we are always near you to protect you and to spread our unconditional love.\n\nHave the Happiest Birthday ever.\n\nAnd as humans say, Gali waala sab dekh rha he. We gali waala are watching and protecting you forever.\n\n\nLove."</string>
    <string name="wishme">"Message from me"</string>
    <string name="wishme2">"Dear friend,

Many years have passed since we met on the road, who was going to tell us! It is a bit of vertigo to look back because, when you do, it is when you realize that the years go by too fast. However, you also realize how wonderful it is to see life move forward and that you still have some people to your side, unconditionally, willing to live everything with you and get the funniest side of everything that happens to you.

Gone are all the afternoons of the university in the cafeteria, eating and drinking on the lawn, organizing some classwork. At the same time, we wanted to go home or staying to stay for dinner and then go out to party with great makeup and ready to give everything dancing. Those times were good, but I wouldn’t trade them for what we have today. Not for nothing, but because a lot of things have happened to us along the way, we have been evolving, changing, living longer, and we have done all that together. Can you ask a friend for something more beautiful?

They say that birthdays are the perfect opportunity to make a ‘remember’ of those things and I can’t agree more! Today, on your birthday, I go back to college and our “innocent” expectations to review each of the trips we have made together (and their anecdotes). Missing a train at minus 11 degrees? Make friends from other countries? Cry with laughter at any anecdote? Tirelessly planning a trip? Throw ourselves on the beach to reflect on life and our plans for the future? Tell us the past without fear of judging ourselves? I would live every moment with you again. We have cried, we have accompanied each other in bad times, and we have been happy for all the good ones because, after all, that is what friendship consists of. And when a certain date arrives, like your birthday, I cannot be happier to continue adding plots and years to our history. I’m so glad to have you as a friend.

Finally, in this year that you start, I am not going to wish you the typical (otherwise, it would not be me). I wish you this “new year” that begins today to laugh until your abs hurt (those that will never hurt from playing sports, and you know it), that they surprise you until you drop your jaw, that you hug (in the distance) as if the most distant were by your side and, above all, that you learn to appreciate the details that this new stage has prepared for you. Because at the end of the day, that’s what happiness and life consist of. In making the most of those details and knowing how to value them.

I’m sure there will be a lot of good things coming to you. Happy Birthday!

Your friend loves you. "</string>
</resources>
